HONG MIN-BEOM
홍민범
Gang-yong?
강용?
Yes. I'll be there in ten minutes.
그렇습니다. 10분 후에 도착하겠습니다.
Min-beom, don't hang up.
민범아, 전화 끊지 마.
Stavi mobile na stol
Stavi mobile na stol
to be able to listen. Do you understand?
들을 수 있다는 것. 이해하셨나요?
Let's cut to the chase.
추격전을 시작합시다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Don't act like a child and be calm.
어린아이처럼 굴지 말고 침착하게 행동하세요.
GANG-YONG
강용
Do you hear me?
내 말 들리나요?
Bastard, how are you talking to me?
개자식아, 나한테 어떻게 얘기하는 거야?
Do you want to die?
죽고 싶나요?
You're making a big mistake, you fucking criminal!
넌 큰 실수를 하고 있어, 이 빌어먹을 범죄자야!
Shut up.
입 다물어.
Gang-yong.
강용.
- Quiet! - I'll make sure you end up in jail!
- 조용한! - 꼭 감옥에 가두겠습니다!
Kurvin sine!
커빈 사인!
Fuck! Shut up, dumbass!
못쓰게 만들다! 닥쳐, 멍청아!
A fool.
바보.
Have you calmed down now?
이제 진정됐나요?
Answer me.
대답 해.
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원하세요?
A report was received at the police station today .
오늘 경찰서에 신고가 접수되었습니다 .
A guy on a motorcycle slit a man's throat in the parking lot and ran away.
오토바이를 탄 남성이 주차장에서 남성의 목을 그은 뒤 달아났습니다.
Write this down.
이것을 적어보세요.
Alone, Gangdong, A 6438.
나홀로, 강동, A 6438.
It's a fake table number , so it won't be in the database.
이는 가짜 테이블 번호이므로 데이터베이스에 포함되지 않습니다.
Find out where the guy on the motorcycle is.
오토바이를 탄 남자가 어디에 있는지 알아보세요.
To find out...
알아내려면...
I know it won't be easy.
쉽지 않을 거라는 걸 알아요.
That's why I called you.
그래서 내가 당신에게 전화한 거예요.
It is now 10 pm. I give you five hours.
지금은 오후 10시입니다. 5시간을 드리겠습니다.
If you don't find it,
찾지 못하시면,
your cousin's striptease will end up on the internet.
네 사촌의 스트립쇼가 인터넷에 올라올 거야.
Try to row me over and the same thing will happen.
나를 노려봐 도 같은 일이 일어날 것입니다.
If you don't want Group Iil share prices to fall tomorrow morning,
내일 오전 그룹일 주가 하락을 원하지 않는다면
listen to me
내 말 좀 들어봐
What is the code?
코드는 무엇입니까?
735629.
735629.
See you.
또 봐요.
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
CHASERS
체이서
Good evening.
좋은 저녁이에요.
- Come, poor thing. - Hello!
- 와, 불쌍한 것. - 안녕하세요!
Damn it.
젠장.
I'll buy you a drink.
내가 한 잔 사줄게.
- This way. - Thank you.
- 이 방법. - 감사합니다.
- Sir. - Hello.
- 선생님. - 안녕하세요.
They cook the body for days until the bones are soft.
뼈가 부드러워질 때까지 며칠 동안 몸을 요리합니다 .
Then they grind them up and throw them into the ocean.
그런 다음 그것을 갈아서 바다에 버립니다.
It costs 15 million per body.
한 몸에 1500만 원이 듭니다.
We won't find a single bone.
우리는 뼈 하나도 찾지 못할 것입니다.
Who cooks people? What patients.
누가 사람을 요리하나요? 어떤 환자.
How do you know that?
어떻게 알았어?
Seung-deok told me.
승덕이가 말해줬어요.
He is in prison. How does he know about it?
그는 감옥에 있습니다. 그는 그것에 대해 어떻게 알 수 있습니까?
Prison is always the fastest source of information.
감옥은 언제나 가장 빠른 정보원이다.
Guys, are you okay?
여러분, 괜찮으세요?
- We're.
- 이었다.
It was not easy to witness that.
그것을 목격하는 것은 쉽지 않았습니다.
What will happen when the casino opens?
카지노가 열리면 어떻게 될까요?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Myeong-gil will collect the money.
명길이 돈을 모을 것이다.
- I understand. - Gun-woo.
- 이해합니다. - 건우.
And?
그리고?
Gamblers and drug addicts often take out private loans.
도박꾼과 마약 중독자들은 종종 개인 대출을 받습니다.
Myeong-gil wants to connect gambling and money lending.
명길은 도박과 자금대출을 연결하고 싶어한다.
The more people visit his casino, the more people will take out loans.
더 많은 사람들이 그의 카지노를 방문할수록 더 많은 사람들이 대출을 받을 것입니다.
Money will come in every day.
매일 돈이 들어올 것입니다.
But only foreigners can go to casinos.
하지만 카지노에는 외국인만 갈 수 있어요.
That is not an obstacle for him.
그것은 그에게 장애물이 아닙니다.
Aha.
아하.
Big clients will be let in the back.
큰 고객은 뒤로 물러날 것입니다.
They won't make much money legally.
그들은 법적으로 많은 돈을 벌지 못할 것입니다.
When he earns enough money, he will take out a loan and buy a building.
돈을 충분히 벌면 대출을 받아 건물을 살 것이다.
She will be his collateral
그녀는 그의 담보가 될 것이다
for a bigger loan and the purchase of an even bigger building.
더 큰 대출과 더 큰 건물 구입을 위해.
That bastard is very resourceful.
그 놈은 아주 수완이 풍부해요.
He will increase activities in the casino to pay back the loan.
그는 대출금을 갚기 위해 카지노에서의 활동을 늘릴 것입니다 .
And Smile Capital will squeeze even more people.
그리고 스마일캐피탈은 더 많은 사람들을 짜낼 것입니다.
Myeong-gil will gain control over everyone.
명길은 모든 사람을 통제하게 될 것이다.
Myeong-gil stole more than 20 billion won from me back then.
명길은 그때 나에게서 200억 원이 넘는 돈을 훔쳤다.
When we return them,
우리가 그것들을 돌려줄 때,
shall we travel the world with Gun-woo and Woo-jin?
건우, 우진과 함께 세계여행을 떠나볼까요 ?
And now we have enough money.
그리고 이제 우리는 돈이 충분합니다.
And,
그리고,
but we can't go anywhere because of corona.
하지만 우리는 코로나 때문에 아무데도 갈 수가 없어요.
Pa...
아빠...
We're going to Rome.
우리는 로마로 갈 거예요.
Why there?
왜 거기?
When I was 20 years old, I saw the movie Holiday in Rome.
스무 살 때 영화 을 봤다.
I swore I'd go there after I got rich,
부자가 된 후에 거기에 가겠다고 맹세했는데 ,
but I didn't have a chance.
하지만 기회가 없었어요.
I thought it would be nice if we went,
같이 가면 좋을 것 같았는데,
four of us.
우리 넷.
I'll buy you anything you want.
당신이 원하는 것은 무엇이든 사줄게요.
Grandpa, there are many expensive things in Italy.
할아버지, 이탈리아에는 비싼 것들이 많아요.
It is a land of luxury.
사치의 땅이다.
Who do you think you're talking to?
누구랑 얘기하고 있는 것 같나요?
You will see how the money is spent.
돈이 어떻게 쓰이는지 볼 수 있을 것이다.
Grandpa, it's called "flexing".
할아버지, 그걸 '플렉싱'이라고 해요.
Yes, I will show you "flexing".
네, "굴곡"을 보여드리겠습니다.
You show nothing. You're just flexing.
당신은 아무것도 보여주지 않습니다. 당신은 단지 유연성을 발휘하고 있습니다.
Flexible
유연한
Well, when all this is over, we'll all travel there together.
글쎄, 이 모든 일이 끝나면 우리는 모두 함께 그곳으로 여행을 떠날 것입니다.
Yes sir?
알겠습니다?
Yeah, that sounds good.
네, 좋은 것 같아요.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
Mr. Choi invited us for a drink at his place.
최씨는 우리를 자기 집으로 초대했다.
I guess he's in a good mood.
그 사람 기분이 좋은 것 같아요.
Do you two drink?
둘이서 술을 마시나요?
We're coming!
오고 있었다!
Can you speed up?
속도를 높일 수 있나요?
Double or quadruple?
더블 또는 쿼드러플?
- Double. - Good.
- 더블. - 좋은.
If I were Kim Myeong-gil,
내가 김명길이었다면,
I would move the hard drive to a more secure location
하드 드라이브를 더 안전한 위치로 옮기겠습니다.
fearing that Im Jang-do had blurted it all out.
임장도가 모든 것을 흐릿하게 말한 것을 두려워했다.
Do you think you could pull it off?
당신이 그것을 해낼 수 있다고 생각합니까?
We took away his main helpers.
우리는 그의 주요 도우미를 제거했습니다.
Now there is no one to mobilize but Jung.
이제 정씨 외에는 동원할 사람이 없다.
In addition,
게다가,
I don't think he would trust that information to anyone.
나는 그가 그 정보를 누구에게도 신뢰하지 않을 것이라고 생각합니다 .
He doesn't have to move it far.
그는 멀리 이동할 필요가 없습니다.
He can put it in the trunk.
그는 그것을 트렁크에 넣을 수 있습니다.
He is aware of that.
그는 그것을 알고 있습니다.
You're right.
네가 옳아.
If we could win his enemies to our side,
만일 우리가 그의 적들을 우리 편으로 끌어들일 수 있다면 ,
that would be to our advantage.
그것은 우리에게 유리할 것입니다.
But for that we need a hard drive.
하지만 그러기 위해서는 하드 드라이브가 필요합니다.
The disk contains a lot of information about his victims of blackmail.
디스크에는 협박 피해자에 대한 많은 정보가 포함되어 있습니다 .
These people have the same motive as us.
이 사람들도 우리와 같은 동기를 가지고 있습니다.
There must be many powerful individuals like Group Iil's successor.
Group Iil의 후계자처럼 강력한 인물이 많을 것입니다 .
The longer this goes on, the worse off we are.
이런 일이 오래 지속될수록 우리의 상황은 더욱 악화됩니다.
Myeong-gil has already established a wide network of acquaintances.
명길은 이미 폭넓은 지인 네트워크를 구축해 왔다.
He must have already bribed all the policemen, prosecutors and politicians
이미 경찰, 검찰, 정치인 모두에게 뇌물을 줬나 봐요.
which he could.
그는 할 수 있었다.
If we relax even for a moment, it will harm us.
잠시라도 긴장을 풀면 우리에게 해를 끼칠 것입니다.
And.
그리고.
Still, we took three men from him, didn't we?
그래도 우리는 그에게서 남자 세 명을 데려갔죠, 그렇죠?
It discourages planning too far in advance.
너무 미리 계획하는 것을 권장하지 않습니다.
But as far as it seems to me, we started well.
하지만 제가 보기에 우리는 잘 시작했습니다.
No one was injured.
아무도 부상을 입지 않았습니다.
Truth.
진실.
We do things one at a time.
우리는 한 번에 하나씩 일을 합니다.
Let's take down Myeong-gil first, then his company.
먼저 명길을 무너뜨리고, 그다음 그의 회사를 무너뜨리자.
Besides, now that Im Jang-do and Kim Jun-min are gone,
게다가 임장도와 김준민도 사라진 지금 ,
he will surely come to his senses.
그는 반드시 정신을 차릴 것이다.
I guess you're right.
난 당신이 옳은 것 같아요.
This one...
이 하나...
And.
그리고.
Mr. Choi. Ladies and gentlemen.
최 씨. 신사숙녀 여러분.
I would like to toast our safety and our common goal.
나는 우리의 안전과 공동의 목표를 축하하고 싶습니다 .
When I say "Let's find that disk,"
내가 "그 디스크를 찾아보자"고 말하면,
you say, "Kim Myeong-gil is done"
김명길은 끝났다고 하네
as a continuation of the toast.
토스트의 연속으로.
Let's begin. Raise your glasses.
의 시작하자. 안경을 들어보세요.
Let's find that disc. Kim Myeong-gil is...
그 디스크를 찾아보자. 김명길은...
- Gotov!
- 고토프!
I'm going to Joongang station.
중앙역으로 갑니다.
They moved from Dongpa-gu district to Joongang-gu.
동파구에서 중앙구로 이사했습니다.
Can you find them by 3 o'clock?
3시까지 찾을 수 있나요?
They can if they stopped in Joongang-gu,
중앙구에 들르면 그럴 수 있지.
but if they moved to another district,
하지만 다른 지역으로 이사했다면,
I'll have to keep looking.
계속 찾아봐야겠어요.
Help me.
도와주세요.
Don't worry.
걱정하지 마세요.
For now, we'll do what the bastard wants.
지금은 그 놈이 원하는 대로 할게요.
And when this is over, I'll figure out how to screw him up.
그리고 이 일이 끝나면 나는 그를 망칠 방법을 알아낼 것입니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Min-beom, you think I'd let some jerk screw my family?
민범아, 내가 어떤 멍청이가 우리 가족을 망치게 놔둘 것 같아?
Do not worry.
걱정 하지마.
Dobro?
도브로?
I only have you.
나에겐 너밖에 없어.
Don't drink too much, okay?
너무 많이 마시지 마세요, 그렇죠?
And.
그리고.
God. Why did he drink so much if he can't stand drinking?
하나님. 그는 술을 참을 수 없는데 왜 그렇게 많이 마셨는가 ?
Maybe he was
어쩌면 그는 그랬을지도 몰라
especially good will.
특히 좋은 뜻.
I am sleepy. And you?
나는 졸린다. 당신은요?
I'm going back down.
나는 다시 내려갈 것이다.
- Aren't you tired? - No, I'm fine.
- 피곤하지 않아? - 아냐 난 괜찮아.
Well done for today.
오늘은 잘 했어요.
Of course.
물론.
Gun-woo.
건우.
You do not sleep?
잠이 안 오나요?
Not. Why are you awake?
아니다. 왜 깨어 있나요?
We relax with a drink.
우리는 음료를 마시며 휴식을 취합니다.
- Do you drink too? - Of course not.
- 너도 마셔? - 당연히 아니지.
God.
하나님.
In the morning I will make a hangover soup.
아침에는 해장국을 만들어 보겠습니다.
It can. Sleep. I'll close the door.
그럴 수 있다. 잠. 문을 닫을게요.
Good. Sleep tight.
좋은. 잘 자.
Good night.
안녕히 주무세요.
Nice to have a drink with you after so long.
오랜만에 같이 한잔하게 되어 반갑습니다 .
Some woman?
어떤 여자요?
And.
그리고.
Who would call you at this time?
이 시간에 누가 당신에게 전화하겠습니까?
Tell me.
말해 주세요.
Yang-jung.
양정.
I'm going to be a dad.
나는 아빠가 될 것이다.
What?
무엇?
In two months. It's a girl.
두 달 안에. 소녀입니다.
I have been with her mother for three years.
나는 그녀의 어머니와 3년 동안 함께 지냈습니다.
You should have told me you had a family, you wretch!
나한테 가족이 있다고 말했어야지 , 이 불쌍한 놈아!
Then he would tell me not to come.
그러면 그 사람은 나한테 오지 말라고 하더군요.
Go home. I'll be leaving soon too.
집에가. 나도 곧 떠날 예정이다.
No, we haven't been drinking together for a long time.
아니요, 우리는 오랫동안 함께 술을 마시지 않았습니다.
I'm staying.
나는 남을거야.
I said you were going home.
나는 당신이 집에 간다고 말했다.
Man, that temper of yours.
이봐, 그 성격.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Thanks, I don't need it.
고마워요. 필요하지 않아요.
It's not for you. Buy the woman some meat.
그것은 당신을 위한 것이 아닙니다. 그 여자에게 고기를 사주세요.
Iron intake is important for pregnant women. Come on.
임산부에게는 철분 섭취가 중요합니다. 어서 해봐요.
This is too much.
이건 너무해요.
Are you coming?
당신은 오고 있나요?
Yes, I will now.
네, 지금 그럴게요.
- Good. I'll be down. - Alright.
- 좋은. 나는 내려갈 것이다. - 괜찮은.
Call a taxi.
택시를 부르세요.
I'll light another one while you wait.
기다리는 동안 하나 더 켜 놓겠습니다.
Yang-jung.
양정.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
You are talking nonsense.
당신은 말도 안되는 소리를하고 있습니다.
You are the best.
너는 최고야.
I will buy hanwoo beef on the way back.
돌아가는 길에 한우 쇠고기를 사올게요.
Hyeon-ju said she was going to bed.
현주는 자러 간다고 말했다.
Good.
좋은.
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
Yes I am.
네, 그렇습니다.
You must be very worried.
당신은 매우 걱정해야합니다.
I taught Myeong-gil. He is my responsibility.
나는 명길에게 가르쳤다. 그는 내 책임입니다.
But after my body betrayed me,
하지만 내 몸이 나를 배신한 후,
I didn't have the courage
용기가 없었어
fight with him.
그와 싸워라.
The only thing I could do
내가 할 수 있는 유일한 일은
it was to take care of Hyeon.
현을 보살피기 위해서였다.
Who are you?
누구세요?
Pa,
아빠,
I'm a friend
나는 친구이다
your dad's.
네 아버지의 것.
Do not Cry.
울지 마세요.
Please do not.
이러지마 제발.
Tata!
안녕!
TOUGH
힘든
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Fill this hall
이 홀을 가득 채우세요
the most beautiful flowers for a funeral.
장례식에 가장 아름다운 꽃.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
Bring ten men to guard the coffin transport.
관 수송을 경비할 사람 10명을 데려오세요 .
- Shall we arm them? - No.
- 무장할까요? - 아니요.
Bring them because the girl is alone.
그 소녀가 혼자이기 때문에 그것을 가져 오십시오.
Let them feed her.
그들이 그녀에게 먹이를 주도록 하세요.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
Sir, I think you left the scarf inside.
선생님, 스카프를 안에 두고 오신 것 같아요 .
No, it doesn't matter.
아니요, 상관없습니다.
By the way, why did he kill himself?
그런데 그는 왜 자살했는가?
He worked as a delivery boy in the morning, in the factory during the day,
아침에는 배달원으로, 낮에는 공장에서,
and at night as a driver.
밤에는 운전사로.
He slept three hours working night shifts to save his daughter.
그는 딸을 구하기 위해 야간 근무를 하면서 3시간 동안 잠을 잤습니다.
He lived like that for two years.
그는 2년 동안 그렇게 살았다.
His daughter recovered. Why would you kill yourself?
그의 딸이 회복되었습니다. 왜 자살하겠습니까?
I don't see the reason.
이유가 보이지 않습니다.
I loaned him money without interest.
나는 그에게 이자 없이 돈을 빌려주었다.
He owed only the principal.
그는 원장에게만 빚을 졌습니다.
I told him that I would extend his repayment indefinitely.
나는 그에게 상환을 무기한 연장 하겠다고 말했습니다 .
I'll look into it.
내가 조사해 볼게요.
I do not understand.
난 이해가 안 돼요.
There.
거기.
Third floor.
3 층.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
You scared me.
너는 나를 놀래 켰다.
Are you going to Mr. Cha Sang-ho's funeral?
차상호씨 장례식에 가시나요?
Idem.
같은 저자.
Two years ago I had back surgery and could not lift things.
2년 전에 허리 수술을 받았는데 물건을 들어올릴 수 없었습니다.
Hyeon-jun's father took out the trash for me for three months.
현준이 아버지가 3개월간 쓰레기를 나 대신 버려주셨다.
God.
하나님.
He was extremely kind and hardworking.
그는 매우 친절하고 열심히 일했습니다.
I felt very sorry for Hyeon.
현이한테 너무 미안했어요.
That poor thing was sick and motherless.
그 불쌍한 사람은 아프고 엄마도 없었습니다.
I fed her and filled their refrigerator
나는 그녀에게 먹이를 주고 그들의 냉장고를 채워주었다
so that they don't run out of food.
음식이 떨어지지 않도록.
Why would such a man kill himself now that Hyeon-ju has recovered?
현주가 회복됐는데 왜 그런 남자가 자살을 하겠는가 ?
It's because of those damn moneylenders!
저 빌어먹을 사채업자들 때문이야!
They came whenever they wanted,
그들은 원할 때마다 왔고,
they grabbed him by the neck and beat him.
그들은 그의 목을 잡고 때렸습니다.
Oh God.
오 맙소사.
Describe them.
설명해보세요.
One was built like a bear,
하나는 곰처럼 지어졌고,
and the other was very tall.
다른 하나는 키가 매우 컸습니다.
A month later
한 달 후
another person to whom I lent money killed himself.
내가 돈을 빌려준 또 다른 사람이 자살했습니다.
I also gave her an interest-free loan because she had a sick family member.
나는 또한 그녀에게 아픈 가족이 있었기 때문에 무이자 대출을 해주었습니다 .
I'm going home too early.
집에 너무 일찍 갈 거예요.
Watch out for the stairs.
계단을 조심하세요.
God, my brother.
맙소사, 내 형제.
I'm going now.
나는 지금 간다.
- Have a safe trip home. - Thank you.
- 집까지 안전하게 다녀오세요. - 감사합니다.
Good night.
안녕히 주무세요.
Yang-jung later found out
나중에 알게 된 양정
that Myeong-gil was visiting the people I gave loans to
내가 대출해준 사람들을 명길이 방문했다는 것
for the treatment of their family.
가족의 치료를 위해.
He billed them every month
그는 매달 비용을 청구했어요
several million to extend the loan
대출 연장에 수백만 달러
telling them that I ordered it.
내가 주문했다고 말해요.
My mom fell for the same trick.
우리 엄마도 같은 속임수에 빠졌어요.
There was a hidden clause in the contract.
계약서에 숨겨진 조항이 있었습니다.
I understand.
이해합니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
Many have died because of me.
나 때문에 많은 사람이 죽었습니다.
It's not true.
그것은 사실이 아닙니다.
You have nothing to be sorry for, Mr. Choi.
미안해하실 것 없어요, 최 선생님.
You have a strong sense of responsibility
당신은 책임감이 강해요
and that's why you feel so guilty.
그래서 당신은 죄책감을 느낍니다.
Those who have no shame feel no guilt.
부끄러움이 없는 사람은 죄책감을 느끼지 않습니다.
They always blame others and take advantage of those weaker than themselves.
그들은 항상 남을 비난 하고 자신보다 약한 사람들을 이용합니다.
I believe we are all gathered here because of your good deeds.
여러분의 선행 덕분에 우리 모두가 여기 모였다고 믿습니다 .
I don't think Hyeon-ju knows that you bought the orphanage for her,
현주는 당신이 자기를 위해 고아원을 사준 걸 모르는 것 같은데 ,
but he trusts you with all his heart.
하지만 그는 온 마음을 다해 당신을 신뢰합니다.
We will stop Kim Myeong-gil at all costs.
반드시 김명길을 저지하겠습니다 .
So stop blaming yourself
그러니 자신을 비난하지 마세요.
and take care of your health.
그리고 건강 조심하세요.
When this is all over, I'll get you your own gym
이 모든 일이 끝나면 내가 너만의 체육관을 마련해줄게
where you can focus on training until you become a champion.
챔피언이 될 때까지 훈련에 집중할 수 있는 곳입니다 .
I'm going to build a nice big cafe for your mom on the first floor .
나는 1층에 너희 엄마를 위한 멋지고 큰 카페를 지을 거야.
They won't pay the rent as long as I live.
내가 살아있는 한 그들은 집세를 내지 않을 것입니다.
Pa...
아빠...
Don't know what to say?
무슨 말을 해야 할지 모르시나요?
Yes.
예.
Maybe "thank you".
어쩌면 "고마워요"일 수도 있습니다.
And.
그리고.
Thank you, Mr. Choi.
고마워요, 최 선생님.
Yes.
예.
I should thank you.
감사해야겠습니다.
You teach me what youth is.
젊음이 무엇인지 가르쳐주세요.
This is...
이것은...
flexing!
굴곡!
You like it?
당신은 그것을 좋아합니까?
And.
그리고.
See here.
여기를 보아라.
- Here? - No, next to it.
- 여기? - 아니, 그 옆에요.
Good.
좋은.
And that part?
그리고 그 부분은?
- Thank you. - Nothing.
- 감사합니다. - 아무것도 아님.
Bravo.
브라보.
GANG-YONG
강용
- Fall? - Onyu-ro 88.
- 떨어지다? - 온유로 88.
Happy?
행복하다?
Thanks for the effort.
노력해 주셔서 감사합니다.
- Let's go. - Yes sir!
- 갑시다. - 알겠습니다!
Stop.
멈추다.
Looks like Choi is on crutches now.
최씨는 지금 목발을 짚고 있는 것 같다.
They tortured Jang-do with salt.
장도를 소금으로 고문했다.
Did he snitch on us?
그 사람이 우리를 밀고한 걸까요?
I'm not sure.
잘 모르겠습니다.
In this case, we can assume that it is.
이 경우 그렇다고 가정할 수 있습니다.
We'll get rid of Choi first,
우선 최씨를 없애자.
a onda Jang-doa.
아온다 장도아.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
Sir.
선생님.
LEE DU-YONG
이두용
Be careful not to accidentally kill him.
실수로 그를 죽이지 않도록 조심하세요.
I have to ask him something.
그에게 물어볼 게 있어요.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
And get it out of your ears.
그리고 귀에서 꺼내십시오.
Good.
좋은.
Du-yeong.
두영.
I think there's someone at the door.
문 앞에 누군가 있는 것 같아요.
Who is?
누구입니까?
Neighbor from the lower floor.
아래층의 이웃입니다.
Water is leaking from the ceiling.
천장에서 물이 새고 있습니다.
Can I look in your bathroom?
화장실 좀 들여다봐도 될까요?
I promise it won't take long. My apartment is flooded.
오래 걸리지 않을 거라고 약속해요. 내 아파트가 침수되었습니다.
My children can't sleep.
우리 아이들은 잠을 못 자요.
I would be grateful.
감사하겠습니다.
Now?
지금?
That. It won't last long.
저것. 오래 가지 않을 것입니다.
Just to see the situation.
상황을 볼 뿐입니다.
Honey?
꿀?
And?
그리고?
- Who is? - He says his water is leaking.
- 누구죠? - 물이 새고 있다고 하더군요.
- Move. - What?
- 이동하다. - 무엇?
Move over.
더 나아가서.
- Just a moment. - Good.
- 잠시만. - 좋은.
Honey, call the police and report a burglary in progress.
여보, 경찰에 전화해서 강도 사건이 진행 중이라고 신고하세요.
Why?
왜?
I'll explain later.
나중에 설명하겠습니다.
Do you believe me?
당신은 나를 믿습니까?
- Yes. - Another thing.
- 예. - 또 다른 한가지.
Whatever happens,
어떤 일이,
don't open the door.
문을 열지 마세요.
Good.
좋은.
It's okay, honey.
괜찮아, 얘야.
Nothing will happen.
아무것도 안 일어날거야.
Jesus.
예수.
Okrug Dongjak-gu.
오크룩 동작구.
Please hurry. My husband is in danger.
서둘러주세요. 남편이 위험에 빠졌어요.
Quick, get in.
빨리 들어가세요.
Let's get him out.
그를 내보내자.
What the fuck?
뭐야?
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
Shit. Nasty!
똥. 끔찍한!
Gade!
가데!
Smudge! Kurvin sine!
더러움! 커빈 사인!
Get up, asshole!
일어나, 이 새끼야!
Curve sine!
곡선 사인!
If you tell me where Hwang Yang-jung is,
황양정이 어디 있는지 알려면
I won't kill your wife.
나는 당신의 아내를 죽이지 않을 것입니다.
I always keep my promise.
나는 항상 약속을 지킨다.
Regardless of everything.
모든 것에 관계없이.
Trust me.
날 믿어.
- Did you get enough sleep? - Yes I am.
- 잠은 충분히 잤나요? - 네, 그렇죠.
Did you get enough sleep?
잠은 충분히 잤나요?
- And you? - Yes I am.
- 당신은요? - 네, 그렇죠.
Come.
오다.
I can't believe this is happening.
나는 이런 일이 일어나고 있다는 것을 믿을 수 없습니다.
That. This is a real reunion.
저것. 이것은 진정한 재회입니다.
Woo-jin, get up. Do you hear me?
우진아, 일어나라. 내 말 들리나요?
Let's eat.
먹자.
- Thank you very much. - You're welcome.
- 매우 감사합니다. - 천만에요.
- Do not come? - He doesn't want to get up.
- 오지마? - 그는 일어나고 싶어하지 않습니다.
He should have eaten and then gone to sleep again.
그는 밥을 먹고 다시 잠에 들었어야 했습니다.
He drank a lot yesterday.
그는 어제 술을 많이 마셨다.
Is.
이다.
And he boasted that he tolerates drinking well.
그리고 그는 술을 잘 참는다고 자랑했다.
Let's eat now.
이제 먹자.
- Thank you.
- 감사합니다.
Thanks for the meal.
음식 고마워요.
- Gun-woo. - Yes?
- 건우. - 예?
When are you taking your mother to the orphanage?
언제 엄마를 고아원에 데려갈 거야?
Grandpa, I'll borrow your car and take them.
할아버지, 제가 차를 빌려서 가져갈게요.
It has been parked for some time. It might be dangerous. Take care.
한동안 주차되어 있습니다. 위험할 수도 있습니다. 잘 지내세요.
- It'll be fine. - Good.
- 괜찮을 거예요. - 좋은.
Shall we go after dinner? It will only take us an hour.
저녁 식사 후에 갈까요? 한 시간밖에 안 걸릴 거예요.
Does this work for you?
이것이 당신에게 효과가 있습니까?
Well, this...
글쎄, 이건...
I think I would feel better if I stayed here and cooked for you.
여기 있으면서 당신을 위해 요리를 해 주면 기분이 좀 나아질 것 같아요 .
Gđo Yoon.
윤고.
I don't want to bother you,
난 당신을 귀찮게하고 싶지 않아요
but can you help us in the orphanage?
그런데 고아원에서 우리를 도와주실 수 있나요?
Your cooking skills are impressive.
당신의 요리 솜씨가 인상적이에요.
Children would love them.
아이들은 그것을 좋아할 것입니다.
This food is amazing.
이 음식은 정말 놀랍습니다.
Mom, that would be the best.
엄마, 그게 최선일 거예요.
Fine, if that helps.
좋아요, 그게 도움이 된다면요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
You're welcome.
천만에요.
Will you eat all the meals even if I'm not here?
내가 여기 없어도 밥은 다 먹을 건가요 ?
I will.
그럴게요.
Take care.
잘 지내세요.
Worry less.
걱정 덜.
I believe in you.
나는 당신을 믿습니다.
Good.
좋은.
SUSHI RESTORAN „HWANGSUSA”
스시 레스토랑 "황수사"
ALARM IS DEACTIVATED
알람이 비활성화되었습니다
Min-dong?
민동?
How did you find me?
나를 어떻게 찾았나요?
Pa,
아빠,
Lee Du-yeong gave me instructions.
이두영 선생님이 지시를 해주셨다.
Did you hurt his wife?
그의 아내에게 상처를 주었나요?
Hello.
안녕하세요.
You killed them?
당신이 그들을 죽였나요?
ONLY 25 KM
단 25km
Let's go.
갑시다.
G. Choi!
G. 최!
- Kim Myeong-gil's men have arrived. - What are you talking about?
-김명길의 부하들이 도착했습니다. - 무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
Let's go to the basement. I have a gun there.
지하실로 가자. 거기에 총이 있어요.
I will stay. Go get the gun.
나는 머물 것이다. 가서 총을 가져오세요.
Hey, Woo-jin!
야, 우진아!
Damn it.
젠장.
- Woo-jin! - Get the gun!
- 우진아! - 총을 가져와!
Woo-jin, come!
우진아, 와!
- Hej, catch ga! - Woo-jin!
- 헤즈, 잡아라! - 우진아!
- Shit.
- 젠장.
Run away!
도망쳐!
Hey curvy sine!
안녕, 곡선 사인!
Quick, get down!
빨리, 내려와!
Fuck!
못쓰게 만들다!
- Come in! - Hey!
- 올! - 여기요!
Curve sine!
곡선 사인!
Hey, go!
이봐, 가!
Tramps!
부랑자!
Hello!
안녕하세요!
Get out!
나가세요!
Shit!
똥!
Curve sine!
곡선 사인!
Fuck it.
젠장.
Woo-jin!
우진!
Where is?
어디에?
This way.
이 방법.
- Pour it out. - Yes sir.
- 부어주세요. - 알겠습니다.
Blood. Hell.
피. 지옥.
Bravo.
브라보.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
I owe you...
나는 당신에게 빚을 지고 있습니다...
gratitude.
고마움.
Here.
여기.
you know,
알잖아,
you gave me a dream
당신은 나에게 꿈을 줬어요
Of...
의...
Therefore...
그러므로...
I will make this painless.
나는 이것을 고통스럽지 않게 만들 것이다.
It is OK.
괜찮아.
It will be over soon. It is OK.
곧 끝날 것입니다. 괜찮아.
Da, evo.
다, 에보.
It is OK.
괜찮아.
Gun-woo.
건우.
- The back door. - Good.
- 뒷문이에요. - 좋은.
Woo-jin!
우진!
Hyeon-ju!
현주!
Hold on.
기다리다.
Grandpa.
할아버지.
God, grandpa.
맙소사, 할아버지.
Stand up.
일어서세요.
Oh God. Gun-woo!
오 맙소사. 건우!
Grandpa!
할아버지!
Gun-woo!
건우!
Grandpa, please get up.
할아버지, 일어나주세요.
Gun-woo, please help.
건우씨, 도와주세요.
Grandpa, please...
할아버지, 제발...
- Hyeon-ju, we have to go out. - No!
- 현주야, 우리 나가야 해. - 아니요!
- We have to. Quickly! - We can not. Let me go!
- 그래야 해요. 빠르게! - 우리는 할 수 없습니다. 날 보내줘!
You will die here!
넌 여기서 죽을 것이다!
Grandpa!
할아버지!
Scalpel.
메스.
Suck the blood! Give me more gauze.
피를 빨아먹어라! 거즈를 더 주세요.
How is the patient?
환자는 어떻습니까?
The pressure is 80/50! The transfusion is starting!
압력은 80/50입니다! 수혈이 시작됩니다!
There is a lack of blood due to COVID. We need it from outside.
코로나로 인해 혈액이 부족합니다. 우리는 외부로부터 그것이 필요합니다.
Give us as much as you can.
가능한 한 많이 주십시오.
Clamp!
집게!
What are we going to do?
우리는 무엇을 할 예정인가요?
- What will we do then? - If anyone else has...
- 그럼 우리는 무엇을 할 것인가? - 다른 사람이 있다면...
- Gun-woo! - What is it?
- 건우! - 그게 뭐죠?
No blood for Woo-jin.
우진에게는 피가 없습니다.
- What? - Which group are you?
- 무엇? - 당신은 어느 그룹인가요?
Group A.
그룹 A.
- Come. - Good.
- 오다. - 좋은.
I will save Woo-jin. Do not worry. Good?
내가 우진이를 구해줄게. 걱정 하지마. 좋은?
Good.
좋은.
He's bleeding profusely.
출혈이 심해요.
Please prepare a lot of blood.
피를 많이 준비해주세요.
I need more gauze.
거즈가 더 필요해요.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
I'm done.
난 끝났어.
Is this enough to save Woo-jin?
우진을 구하기엔 이 정도면 됐지?
We'll need a few more bags.
가방이 몇 개 더 필요해요.
I understand.
이해합니다.
Take another one from me.
나에게서 다른 것을 가져 가라.
More than 320 ml will be risky.
320ml 이상이면 위험합니다.
I'm fine. I'm a boxer. I'll be fine.
잘 지내요. 나는 권투 선수입니다. 난 괜찮을거야.
- I'm fine. - No.
- 잘 지내요. - 아니요.
Please. I really need to save him.
제발. 정말 그를 구해야 해요.
Please get me more blood.
피를 더 뽑아주세요.
- I'm begging you. - I can not.
- 부탁이에요. - 난 못해.
It won't kill me, really.
정말 날 죽이지는 않을 거예요.
Please, I have to save Woo-jin.
제발 우진이를 구해야 해요.
I have to save him.
나는 그를 구해야 해요.
I'm begging you! It won't kill me.
부탁해요! 그것은 나를 죽이지 않을 것입니다.
- I can't see because of the blood. Suck it up! - Here.
- 피 때문에 앞이 안 보여요. 빨아! - 여기.
I can't control the bleeding. Give me a bandage.
출혈을 조절할 수 없습니다. 붕대를 주세요.
The bandage is ready.
붕대가 준비되었습니다.
Good. Prepare more, I'll need them.
좋은. 더 준비하세요. 필요해요.
Blood pressure drops! Please hurry!
혈압이 떨어집니다! 서둘러주세요!